Finding Aid for the James Arkatov Photographs PASC.0340.Coll-level-DAO
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Jazz Musicians, Series 1.
  - Coleman, George, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Coleman, George, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Coleman, George, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Coleman, George, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Coleman, George, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Coleman, George, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Coleman, George, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Collette, Buddy, 1986 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Al Viola.
  - Collette, Buddy, 1986 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Collette, Buddy, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Gerald Wiggins.
  - Colley, Scott, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 2000 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 2000 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Larry Koonse.
  - Colley, Scott, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Colley, Scott, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Chris Potter.
  - Colley, Scott, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Coltrane, Ravi, 2002 June 26; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Condoli, Conti, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Cooper, Craig, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Cooper, Craig, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Cooper, Craig, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Copland, Mark, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Copland, Mark, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Copland, Mark, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Correa, Chick, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Correa, Chick, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Correa, Chick, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Cramer, Larry, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Jane Bunnett.
  - Das, Jayant Kumar, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Das, Jayant Kumar, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davidson, Bill, 1995 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davis, Art, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davis, Art, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davis, Art, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davis, Art, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davis, Art, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davis, Art, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Davis, Art, 1997 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - De Francisco, Joey, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - De Francisco, Joey, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - De Francisco, Joey, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - De Julio, Jim, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Paul Smith.
  - De Julio, Jim, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Diddley, Bo, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Diddley, Bo, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Diddley, Bo, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Diddley, Bo, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Diddley, Bo, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Diddley, Bo, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Diddley, Bo, 1998 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Dorough, Bob, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Dorough, Bob, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Dos Santos, Josias, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With dancer.
  - Dos Santos, Josias, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Dos Santos, Josias, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Duran, Hilario, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Teddy, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Ponomarev, Valery.
  - Edwards, Teddy, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Elliing, Kurt, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Elling, Kurt, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Elling, Kurt, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Elling, Kurt, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Elling, Kurt, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Elliott, Jeff, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Steve Tavaglioni
  - Farmer, Art, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Farmer, Art, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Fisher, Clare, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Fisher, Clare, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Flores, Chuck, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Flores, Chuck, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Foster, Gary, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Foster, Gary, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Lee Konitz
  - Foster, Gary, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Frishberg, Dave, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Frishberg, Dave, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Furgeson, Sherman, 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Gaffney, George, 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Garcia, Cathy Segal, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Garcia, Cathy Segal, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Gibbs, Terry, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Gibbs, Terry, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golea, Vinny, 1998 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golson, Benny, 1999 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golson, Benny, 1999 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Golson, Benny, 1999 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Gonzales, Jerry, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Gonzales, Jerry, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Gonzales, Jerry, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Grapelli, Stephane, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Grisman, David, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Grisman, David, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Grisman, David, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Grisman, David, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Grissett, Danny, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Haden, Charlie, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Haden, Charlie, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Haden, Charlie, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hagans, Tim, 1998 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hamilton, Lynn, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hamilton, Scott, 1997 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Haque, Fareed, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Haque, Fareed, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harrell, Tom, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harrell, Tom, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harrell, Tom, 1997 June 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harrell, Tom, 1997 June 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harris, Stefon, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harrison, Don, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Harrison, Donald Jr., 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hart, Antonio, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hart, Antonio, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heard, John, 1995 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heard, John, 1995 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heard, John, 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heard, John, 1995 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Albert "Tootie", 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Jimmy Heath.
  - Heath, Albert "Tootie", 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Albert "Tootie", 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Jimmy, 1999 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Jimmy, 1999 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Tootie Heath.
  - Heath, Jimmy, 1999 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Percy, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Percy, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Percy, 1999; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Heath, Percy, 8 x 10 b & w (Box 4)
  - Henderson, Bill, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Henderson, Joe, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hill, Andrew, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hill, Andrew, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hill, Andrew, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hill, Andrew, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hill, Andrew, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hobgood, Laurence, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hobgood, Laurence, 1997 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Holland, Dave, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Holland, Dave, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Holland, Dave, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Holland, Dave, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With two unidentified musicians.
  - Holloway, Red, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Holloway, Red, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hughart, Jim, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Hughart, Jim, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With unidentified drummer.
  - Isham, Mark, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Milt, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With John Clayton.
  - Jackson, Milt, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With John Clayton and Tootie Heath at Catalina Bar & Grill.
  - Jackson, Milt, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Milt, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Milt, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Milt, 1996 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jackson, Milt, 1998 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With the Clayton Hamilton Jazz Orchestra
  - Jackson, Milt, 1998 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With unidentified musicians.
  - Jamal, Ahmad, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jamal, Ahmad, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jazz Tap Ensemble, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    Performed at the Jazz Bakery.
  - Jolly, Pete, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jolly, Pete, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jones, Elvin, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    Elvin Jones Jazz Machine.
    Two copies
  - Jones, Elvin, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Jones, Elvin, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Katz, Fred, 1999 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1999 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1999 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1999 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1999 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kellaway, Roger, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Keyes, Calvin, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Keyes, Calvin, 1996; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Keyes, Calvin, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Keyes, Calvin, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Keyes, Calvin, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Big John Patton.
  - Keyes, Calvin, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kitt, Eartha, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Kitt, Eartha, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Konitz, Lee, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Konitz, Lee, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Gary Foster.
  - Konitz, Lee, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Koonse, Larry, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Scott Colley.
  - Koonse, Larry, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Koonse, Larry, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - La Babera, Joe, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Cecil Payne, Nick Brignola and Putter Smith.
  - La Barbara, Joe, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - La Barbara, Joe, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - La Barbera, Joe, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Land, Harold, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Land, Harold, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Land, Harold, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Laws, Hubert, 1999 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Laws, Hubert, 1999 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Laws, Hubert, 1999 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Laws, Ronnie, 1999 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Laws, Ronnie, 1999 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Laws, Ronnie, 1999 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Laws, Ronnie, 1999 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Levief, Milcho, 2000; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Levy, Lou, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lincoln, Abbey, 1980 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lincoln, Abbey, 1980 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lincoln, Abbey, 1980 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lincoln, Abbey, 1980 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lincoln, Abbey, 1980 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Littleton, Jeff, 1999 November; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Jazz Quartet, 2001 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Jazz Quartet, 2001 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Jazz Quartet, 2001 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Jazz Quartet, 2001 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Los Angeles Jazz Quartet, 2001 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lovano, Joe, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Cecil Mcbee.
  - Lovano, Joe, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lovano, Joe, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Lundy, Carmen, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Billy Childs.
  - Lundy, Carmen, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mangione, Chuck, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mangione, Chuck, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mangione, Chuck, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Branford, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Branford, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Branford, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Branford, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Branford, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Delfayo, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Delfayo, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Delfayo, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Delfayo, 1996 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Marsalis, Wynton, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Martin, Mel, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Maupin, Bennie, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Maupin, Bennie, 1999 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mayo, Scott, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mayo, Scott, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mayo, Scott, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Dori Caymmi.
  - Mayuto, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mayuto, 1996 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McBee, Cecil, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Joe Lovano.
  - McBride, Christian, 2001 August 17; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    UCLA performance.
  - McBride, Christian, 2001 August 17; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McBride, Christian, 2001 August 17; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McBride, Christian, 2001 August 17; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McBride, Christian, 2001 August 17; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McBride, Christian, 2001 August 17; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McBride, Christian, 2001 August 17; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McCann, Les, 1999 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McCann, Les, 1999 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 1999 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 2001 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 2001 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 2001 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mcferrin, Bobbie, 2001 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McKenna, Dave, 1997 June 10; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McKenna, Dave, 1997 June 10; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McLean, Jackie, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McLean, Jackie, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - McLean, Jackie, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Cedar Walton.
  - McPartridge, Marian, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Meeks, Charles, 1997 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mehldau, Brad, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mehldau, Brad, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mehldau, Brad, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Mehldau, Brad, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Ruth Price
  - Parker, Leon, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Parks, Dean, 2000 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Pasqua, Alan, 2001 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Pasqua, Alan, 2001 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Pasqua, Alan, 2001 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Pasqua, Alan, 2001 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Patton, Big John, 2000 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Calvin Keyes.
  - Payne, Cecil, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Nick Brignola.
  - Payne, Cecil, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Nick Brignola, Putter Smith and Joe La Barbera.
  - Payne, Cecil, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Payne, Cecil, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Payne, Cecil, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Payton, Nicholas, 1996 May 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Payton, Nicholas, 1996 May 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Payton, Nicholas, 1996 May 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Payton, Nicholas, 1996 May 15; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Penn, Clarence, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Person, Eric, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Person, Eric, 1997 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Pisano, John, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Pisano, John, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Ponomarev, Valery, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Teddy Edwards.
  - Ponomarev, Valery, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Ponomarev, Valery, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Potter, Chris, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Potter, Chris, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Potter, Chris, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Potter, Chris, 2001 June 19; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Price, Ruth, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Price, Ruth, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Price, Ruth, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Brad Mehldau.
  - Price, Ruth, 1995 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Printup, Marcus, 1998 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Printup, Marcus, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Redman, Joshua, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Reid, Rich, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Ritchie Cole Group, 2000 July; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Roach, Max, 1998 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With ensemble.
  - Roach, Max, 1998 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roach, Max, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roach, Max, 1998 April; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1997 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roberts, Marcus, 1996 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rogers, Adam, 2002 June 25; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rollins, Sonny, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    At the House of Blues.
  - Rollins, Sonny, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rollins, Sonny, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Roney, Wallace, 1997 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Antoine Roney.
    At Catalina Bar & Grill.
  - Roney, Wallace, 1997 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rubelcara, Gonzalo, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rubelcara, Gonzalo, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rubelcara, Gonzalo, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rubelcara, Gonzalo, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rubelcara, Gonzalo, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rubelcara, Gonzalo, 1997 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Ruiz, Hilton, 2001 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Ruiz, Hilton, 2001 January; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rushen, Patrice, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rushen, Patrice, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Rushen, Patrice, 1996 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Sanchez, David, 2000 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Sanchez, David, 2000 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Sanchez, David, 1998 February; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Terrell Stafford.
  - Sanchez, David, 2000 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Sandoval, Arturo, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Sandoval, Arturo, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Sandoval, Arturo, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shank, Bud, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shank, Bud, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shank, Bud, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shank, Bud, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shank, Bud, 1996 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Mike Wofford.
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shankar, Ravi, 1997 May; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Shearing, George, 1996 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Siegel, Janis, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Siegel, Janis, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Siegel, Janis, 1999 October; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Simkins, Andy, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Simkins, Andy, 1995 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Smith, Paul, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Smith, Paul, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Smith, Paul, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With Jim De Julio
  - Smith, Paul, 1999 August; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Smith, Putter, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Cecil Payne, Nick Brignola and Joe La Barbera.
  - Smith, Putter, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
    With Cecil Payne, Nick Brignola, and Joe La Barbera.
  - Smith, Putter, 1999 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 1)
  - Stafford, Terrell, 1996 December; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
    With David Sanchez.
  - Stewart, Jimmy, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Stewart, Jimmy, 1995 September; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Strazzeri, Frank, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Strazzeri, Frank, 1997 March; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Tabackin, Lew, 1997 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Tabackin, Lew, 1997 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)
  - Tabackin, Lew, 1997 June; 8 x 10 b & w (Box 2)